After you've identified anomalous skew in
发现信号收益中的异常偏斜情形
your signal returns and you think you know the cause, what do you do?
并且找到原因后 该怎么办？
The best strategy for dealing with these types of
处理这些离群值的最佳策略
outliers varies on a case-by-case basis.
视具体情况而定
If you know it's just bad data from the data vendor,
如果你知道是数据供应商提供的数据有误
you can try to fix it by replacing
可以将受影响的数据
the affected data with correct values from a different vendor.
替换成其他供应商的正确数据
If you can't do this,
如果不能这么做
you might try to determine if your research result will be greatly
你应该判断如果将缺失的值替换成任何合理的值
affected if you replace the value with any reasonable value.
是否会显著影响研究结果
For example, the previous day's values.
例如替换成前一天的值
If this isn't going to work,
如果这么做不可行
you might try to figure out whether removing this data row,
你应该弄清楚删除整行
all together, will have any significant effect on your signal research results.
是否对信号研究结果有显著的影响
You are the one in the best position to make this judgment call.
你是做出这些判断的最合适人选
After all, you know the signal the best.
毕竟你最了解交易信号
If you think the extreme values are due to legit market events,
如果你认为极端值是由合法的市场事件造成的
there are a few different things you should think about.
那么你应该考虑几个事项
You might try to find out whether there are many similar occurrences in other stocks.
你需要了解其他股票也出现了类似的情况吗
If there are and if you can identify a common cause for all the extreme values,
如果其他股票也一样 并且你能找到所有极端值的共同原因
you could consider isolating this group of stocks out of the research stock universe.
你可以考虑从股票池中排除这组股票
You should think about what effect this might have on your signal overall.
你应该思考这么做对整体信号有何影响
Here, we're showing several thinly traded small market cap Asian stocks
图中是几支交易量很少的小市值亚洲股票
experiencing large sudden unpredictable price fluctuations.
它们都经历了突然不可预测的股价波动
Another type of stock that experiences
会出现不可预测的
dramatic unpredictable price fluctuations is
另一类价格会急剧波动的股票
the stock of single drug biotechnology companies.
是单一药物生物科技公司的股票
These type of companies evaluation hinges
此类公司的市值取决于各期临床试验阶段
upon the success of various milestones: phase one,two,
成功与否：例如第一阶段 第二阶段
and three drug efficacy trials and FDA approval.
和第三期临床实验阶段及 FDA 批准时
With only one product,
如果只有一种产品
the company is worth a lot if it is successful and very little if it fails.
药物成功后 公司市值将会很高 药物失败了 市值则会非常低
However, the outcome of these binary events is very difficult to predict and to handle.
但是 此类二元事件的结果很难预测和处理
So, quants frequently exclude these stocks from their trading universes.
所以量化分析师常常会把此类股票从股票池里剔除
As one example, the price of the stock of Sage Theraputics,
例如 Sage Theraputics 是一家
a company that makes a postpartum depression drug,
制造产后抗抑郁症药物的公司
jumped from $93 to $167 in
去年 当他们宣布阳性测试结果后
a single day last year when the company announced positive test results.
公司的股价在一天内就从 93 美元上涨到 167 美元
You should also think about whether events you think are legitimate are due to
你还应该思考你认为合法的事件
special market events like corporate earnings or central bank announcement's.
是否由特殊市场事件导致的 例如企业收益或央行通告
Realistically, if you eventually use this signal to build a trading strategy,
实际上 如果最终使用此信号创建交易策略
you might want to think about whether you can avoid these events by,
则需要思考是否能避免此类事件
for example, pausing the strategy in advance of them.
例如在此类事件之前暂停交易策略
If it's possible to do this,
如果能这么做
then you can probably remove these rows and proceed with the research.
那么可以删除这些行并继续展开研究
If you can't pause the strategy ahead of these events,
如果不能在这些事件之前暂停策略
then you're going to need to think about how you will be able to
则需要思考在执行此策略时
avoid losing money when executing this strategy.
如何避免损失金钱
As you can see, a lot of this is common sense.
有很多方法都是常识
You'll always need to think about how you can prevent
你始终需要思考如何避免
the quality of your research results being
离群值使研究结果的质量下降
degraded by outliers and how you can avoid losing money when trading your final strategy.
以及在用最终策略进行交易时如何避免损失金钱